# JUN CHOI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

(647) 833-4549
cjh4549@gmail.com
www.junchoi.dev
GitHub/cjh4549
LinkedIn/junchoi

## SKILLS

HTML CSS SASS JavaScript jQuery React TypeScript Redux Firebase RESTful API Git/GitHub Responsive Design Accessibility Pair Programming

## OTHER SKILLS

- Customer Rapport
- Agile
- Debugging
- CMS
- Jira
- Asana
- Figma
- SalesForce
- Excel

## **EDUCATION**

## WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE BOOTCAMP

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY 2021

MENTAL HEALTH STUDIES UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO 2013 - 2018

## **PROFILE**

I am a front-end developer with experience building applications with JavaScript (ES6+), React, TypeScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS and API integrations. My passion in bringing creative designs and ideas into life through programming motivates me to write codes that are clean, responsive and problem-solving.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **MODERNA IR SITE | LIVE**

jQuery, CMS, SCSS, Figma

- Collaborated closely with implementation managers and product designers regarding layout, functionality and outstanding user interface interactions
- Developed highly scalable features using CMS and jQuery and matched website design as closely to the Figma design

#### WHAT DO YOU NO | LIVE | REPO

React, Firebase, HTML, CSS, Git, API Integration

- Used Datamuse API to fetch homophones of 10 words and asks user to match definition to the correct word
- Group programming among four developers to implement
   UI features using React and Firebase for backend

#### PLANTED | LIVE | REPO

HTML, SCSS, a11y, JavaScript

- Conversion of a PSD design into a pixel perfect multi-page website that that is fully responsive and accessible
- Notable implementations such as version controls via GitHub and BEM naming conventions

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Q4 INC. | DEC 2021 - PRESENT

- Build investor relation websites for major companies such as Moderna, Paypal and Mattel, using JQuery, SCSS, CMS and Figma
- Work closely with cross-functional teams (UX/UI designers and product owners) in an agile environment
- Ensure user experience by maintaining and fixing post production bugs to keep IR data intact

#### **LIENS COORDINATOR**

TRADEREV | MAR 2019 - JUN 2021

- Assisted in launching car dealers onto TradeRev's app and maintain strong customer rapport with 100+ clients via Salesforce
- Built a Puppeteer app to automate vehicle VIN searches on TradeRev app to help the team's overall work volume